I (INDIANA JONES THEME PLAYS) I
-So what did you think?
-It was good.
That's it? "Good"?
(Amy:)I enjoyed it.
(Amy:)When you told me I was going to be
"losing my virginity,"
(Amy:)I didn't think you meant showing me
Raiders of the Lost Ark
(Amy:)for the first time.
(Sheldon:)My apologies.
I chose my words poorly.
(Sheldon:)I should have said
(Sheldon:)you were about to have
your world rocked on my couch.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, thank you for watching it.
It's one of my all-time favorites.
(Amy:)It was very entertaining,
(Amy:)despite the glaring story problem.
(Sheldon:)Story problem?
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Amy...
(Sheldon:)What a dewy-eyed moon-calf you are.
(Sheldon:)Raiders of the Lost Ark is
the love child
(Sheldon:)of Steven Spielberg and George Lucas,
(Sheldon:)two of the most gifted filmmakers
of our generation.
(Sheldon:)I've watched it 36 times,